Hi, I'm Mark, product manager here at
Tessel, and I'm joined by one of our
engineering leads, Gareth. Today we're
going to be talking about Tessel review.
So, what are some of the biggest
challenges you and the team are facing
as you scale things up?
>> We're automating more and more of our
software development. That means more
unattended decisions being made by more
unattended agents. We're adding more
context and more skills to our repo to
help steer those decisions. And we're
doing this without compromising the
quality of the system that we're
building or the quality of the product
we're shipping to our end users. When
something goes wrong and a PR doesn't
meet the functional requirements or hit
the quality bar that we require, you
often track it back to some piece of
context or some skill that has been
poorly written, poorly worded, and is
confusing, and has led the agent astray.
[music]
We're adding a lot of context
continually, but ultimately we're
relying on vibes for it to be good.
>> And this is exactly what we hear from
customers, too. And that's why we built
Tessel review.
You point it at a skill, it tells you
the quality of that skill, and what you
can do to fix it. It's really simple to
run. You just use Tessel review run and
the name of your skill,
and it will have an agent look at the
content of that skill.
It will look at the formatting of it and
make sure it has the right structure.
It'll then also look at the content and
the description of that skill and assess
it on attributes like conciseness,
ambiguity, and clarity, and more. And in
fact, you can customize this to whatever
your organizational needs are.
On top of that, it's really easy to put
this into your CI so that you can reject
skills that don't meet your quality
threshold. And as you can see from this
example, this skill isn't quite there
yet,
but this is really easy to fix. With
Tessel review fix,
we have an agent look at the results
from the Tessel review, apply changes to
the skill, we run the review, and let
you know what's been improved and what's
changed.
>> So, having this in CI, just like a
linter, means we can trust that the
skills are of a high quality regardless
of who's written them.
>> [music]
>> And the customization means I can change
what quality means for the different
bits of the code base.
>> And it's really easy to get started.
Simply use npm install Tessel to get
Tessel installed and then Tessel review
run to assess the quality of your skill.
Thanks for listening.